Guide to the Walter Chauncey Camp Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1875 - 1925; Series I; 13 linear feet (31 boxes)
  - Price, Charles E., 1916 (Box 20, Folder 563)
  - Price, Frank Julian, 1900, 1918 (Box 20, Folder 563)
  - Price, Luther E., 1894, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 563)
  - Price, W. C., 1894 (Box 20, Folder 563)
  - Priest, A. J., 1921 (Box 20, Folder 563)
  - Princeton University(*), 1878, 1888-1898, 1911-1919 (Box 20, Folder 564)
  - Pringle, William B., 1896 (Box 20, Folder 565)
  - Pritchett, Henry S., 1917 (Box 20, Folder 565)
  - Providence Journal Co., 1907 (Box 20, Folder 565)
  - Public High School of New Britain, Connecticut, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 566)
  - Public Ledger, 1909 1922, undated (Box 20, Folder 566)
  - Public Opinion, 1906 (Box 20, Folder 566)
  - Pullman, Raymond W., 1919 (Box 20, Folder 566)
  - Purchasing Agents' Association of Connecticut, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 566)
  - Purdy, Lucia, 1893-1894 (Box 20, Folder 566)
  - Quigley, E.C., 1920,1923 (Box 20, Folder 567)
  - Quill, John, undated (Box 20, Folder 567)
  - Radcliffe, McCluney, 1917 (Box 20, Folder 568)
  - Raferty, W. C., 1921 (Box 20, Folder 568)
  - Rafferty, Charles D., 1910, 1912 (Box 20, Folder 568)
  - Rafferty, T. C., 1893 (Box 20, Folder 568)
  - Randall, A. W., 1894 (Box 20, Folder 568)
  - Randolph, M. P., 1894 (Box 20, Folder 568)
  - Rawle, Francis, 1910 (Box 20, Folder 569)
  - Rawson, A. L., 1900 (Box 20, Folder 569)
  - Raycroft, Joseph E., 1894, 1904-1920, undated (Box 20, Folder 569)
  - Raymond, H. W., 1901 (Box 20, Folder 569)
  - Read, L. H., 1899 (Box 20, Folder 570)
  - Reade, Ralph W. B., 1922 (Box 20, Folder 570)
  - Recreation, 1907 (Box 20, Folder 570)
  - Redfield, H. H., 1899 (Box 20, Folder 570)
  - Redfield, (Scott F.) Publishing Co., 1909, 1911 (Box 20, Folder 570)
  - Reed, Bert, 1919 (Box 20, Folder 571)
  - Reed, Carl A., 1920 (Box 20, Folder 571)
  - Reed, Caroline, undated (Box 20, Folder 571)
  - Reed, Herbert, 1911 (Box 20, Folder 571)
  - Rees, R. R., 1918 (Box 20, Folder 571)
  - Regan, John M., 1911 (Box 20, Folder 571)
  - Reick, W. C., 1893 (Box 20, Folder 571)
  - Reid, William T., Jr.(*), 1892, 1894, 1904-1910, undated (Box 20, Folder 572-573)
    See also: box 1, folder 24
  - Reilly & Britton Co., 1911 (Box 20, Folder 574)
  - Reilly, James, 1912 (Box 20, Folder 574)
  - Reitz, Albert E., 1894 (Box 20, Folder 574)
  - Remington, A. D., 1900 (Box 20, Folder 574)
  - Renou, Edward Jr., 1894 (Box 20, Folder 574)
  - Revels, F. W., 1904 (Box 20, Folder 575)
  - Reynolds Publishing Company(*), 1922-1924 (Box 20, Folder 575)
  - Rhodes, Charles D., 1894-1895 (Box 20, Folder 576)
  - Rhodes, Guy F., 1922 (Box 20, Folder 576)
  - Rhodes, W. C.(*), 1890-1894, 1901, 1903, undated (Box 20, Folder 576)
  - Rice, Charles A., 1893 (Box 21, Folder 577)
  - Rice, Grantland, 1917, undated (Box 21, Folder 577)
  - Rice Leaders of the World Association, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 577)
  - Rice, R. C., 1907 (Box 21, Folder 577)
  - Rich, Clarence A., 1904 (Box 21, Folder 578)
  - Richards, Charles E., 1900 (Box 21, Folder 578)
  - Richards, Eugene Lamb(*), 1883, 1887, 1889-1896, 1899-1900, 1902 (Box 21, Folder 579-581)
  - Richards, Howard, Jr., 1912 (Box 21, Folder 582)
  - Richards, Philip H., 1924 (Box 21, Folder 582)
  - Richardson, D. L., 1905 (Box 21, Folder 582)
  - Richardson, George P., 1902 (Box 21, Folder 582)
  - Richardson James Caffrey, 1893 (Box 21, Folder 582)
  - Richardson, Willis B., 1900, 1902 (Box 21, Folder 582)
  - Ricker, J. M., 1909 (Box 21, Folder 582)
  - Ridgway, M. B., 1919 (Box 21, Folder 583)
  - Rigdon, W. L., 1899 (Box 21, Folder 583)
  - Riggs, Jesse B., 1894 (Box 21, Folder 583)
  - Riggs, T. Dudley, 1909 (Box 21, Folder 583)
  - Rinehart, C. R., 1905-1906, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 583)
  - Ripley, Alfred L., 1893-1894, 1897, 1901-1913 (Box 21, Folder 584)
  - Ripple, P. W, 1913 (Box 21, Folder 585)
  - Ripton, B. H., 1894 (Box 21, Folder 585)
  - Ritchie, John H., 1909-1910, 1917, undated (Box 21, Folder 586)
  - Rix, J. Burton, 1916 (Box 21, Folder 586)
  - Roanoke College, 1911 (Box 21, Folder 587)
  - Robb, W. S., 1911 (Box 21, Folder 587)
  - Robbins, F. W., 1904 (Box 21, Folder 587)
  - Roberts, Charles A., 1911 (Box 21, Folder 587)
  - Roberts, Charles G. D., 1902 (Box 21, Folder 587)
  - Robertson, G. S., 1894 (Box 21, Folder 587)
  - Robertson, Howard, 1899 (Box 21, Folder 587)
  - Robinson, Lucius F., 1889 (Box 21, Folder 588)
  - Robinson Oscar D., 1894 (Box 21, Folder 588)
  - Robinson, Robert, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 588)
  - Rochester, University of, 1900 (Box 21, Folder 588)
  - Rockefeller, Percy A., 1901, 1918 (Box 21, Folder 589)
    See also: box 30, folder 819-821
  - Rockland (Maine) High School, 1893 (Box 21, Folder 589)
  - Rockne, Knute, 1923 (Box 21, Folder 589)
  - Rockwell, Foster H., 1902 (Box 21, Folder 589)
  - Rockwell, H. H., 1922 (Box 21, Folder 589)
  - Rogers, Archibald, 1902 (Box 21, Folder 590)
  - Rogers, Henry Wade, 1911 (Box 21, Folder 590)
  - Rogers, James Gamble, 1909, 1924 (Box 21, Folder 590)
  - Rogers, John, Jr., 1899 (Box 21, Folder 590)
  - Rolling Megaphone Co., [1904] (Box 21, Folder 591)
  - Romeike (Henry) Company, 1899 (Box 21, Folder 591)
  - Romeyer, C. L., 1894 (Box 21, Folder 591)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1917-1920 (Box 21, Folder 592)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore(*), 1895-1896, 1901, 1905-1908, 1915 (Box 21, Folder 593)
  - Root, E. P., 1905 (Box 21, Folder 594)
  - Root, Frederick Stanley, 1894, 1902-1903, undated (Box 21, Folder 594)
  - Roper, Daniel C.(*), 1917 (Box 21, Folder 595)
  - Roper, William W., 1907, 1911, 1917-1919 (Box 21, Folder 596)
  - Roscoe & Roscow, 1924 (Box 21, Folder 597)
  - Rose, William Ganson, 1923-1925, undated (Box 21, Folder 597)
  - Ross, George G., 1894 (Box 21, Folder 597)
  - Rotarian, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 598)
  - Rotary Club:
    - Atlanta, Georgia, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 598)
    - New Haven, Connecticut, 1920 (Box 21, Folder 598)
    - New York City, 1918 (Box 21, Folder 598)
    - San Francisco, 1924 (Box 21, Folder 598)
  - Roycroft Shops, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 598)
  - Rugby Football Union, 1906 (Box 21, Folder 599)
  - Russell, Isaac, 1904 (Box 21, Folder 599)
  - Russell, John E., undated (Box 21, Folder 599)
  - Russell, Thomas H., 1891 (Box 21, Folder 599)
  - Rutgers College, 1893-1894 (Box 21, Folder 600)
  - Rutgers Preparatory School, 1911 (Box 21, Folder 600)
  - Ruth, J. A., 1913 (Box 21, Folder 600)
  - Ryder, E. D., 1906 (Box 21, Folder 600)
  - Sackett, R. C., 1915 (Box 21, Folder 601)
  - St. Albans School, 1894 (Box 21, Folder 601)
  - St. John, L. W., 1909 (Box 21, Folder 601)
  - St. Lawrence University, 1902 (Box 21, Folder 601)
  - St. Louis Post Dispatch, 1910 (Box 21, Folder 601)
  - St. Mark's School, 1894 (Box 21, Folder 601)
  - St. Nicholas (*), 1890, 1893, 1900, 1907-1912 (Box 21, Folder 601)
  - Paul's School, 1894 (Box 21, Folder 601)
  - Salsinger, H. G.(*), 1909, 1921-1923 (Box 21, Folder 602)
  - Sampson, E. V., 1920 (Box 21, Folder 603)
  - Sampson, Martin W., 1892 (Box 21, Folder 603)
  - San Bernardino (California) High School, 1894 (Box 21, Folder 603)
  - San Diego Union, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 603)
  - San Francisco Bulletin, undated (Box 21, Folder 603)
  - San Francisco Chronicle, 1892, 1908 (Box 21, Folder 603)
  - San Francisco Examiner, 1892 (Box 21, Folder 603)
  - Sanchez, Louis A., 1923 (Box 21, Folder 604)
  - Sanderson, Lucien, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 604)
  - Sands, Robert C., 1920 (Box 21, Folder 604)
  - Sandys, Ed. W., 1900 (Box 21, Folder 604)
  - Sanford, D. L., 1891 (Box 21, Folder 605)
  - Sanford, G. Foster, 1905, 1911 (Box 21, Folder 605)
  - Sanford, Leonard C., 1899 (Box 21, Folder 605)
  - Sargent, Dudley A., 1884, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 606)
  - Sargent, Henry B.(*), 1884, 1890-1899, 1901-1917 (Box 21, Folder 606)
  - Saturday Evening Post (*), 1899, 1910, 1912, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 607)
  - Savage, C. W.
    See: box 19, folder 514
  - Savage, Charles W., 1894 (Box 21, Folder 608)
  - Savary, John C., 1916 (Box 21, Folder 608)
  - Sawyer, A. P., 1893-1894, undated (Box 21, Folder 608)
  - Sawyer, George P., 1902-1903, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 608)
  - Scales, E. D., 1898 (Box 21, Folder 609)
  - Schaefer, R. J., 1914 (Box 21, Folder 609)
  - Schmitt, Cooper D., 1894 (Box 21, Folder 609)
  - Schneider, Harry N., Jr., 1903 (Box 21, Folder 609)
  - Schoff, C. H., 1894 (Box 21, Folder 609)
  - Schroeder, Albrect von, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 609)
  - Schroeder, Louis C., 1919 (Box 21, Folder 609)
  - Schultze, Emile, Jr., 1894 (Box 21, Folder 609)
  - Schweppe, Richard J., 1924 (Box 21, Folder 609)
  - Scientific American, 1903 (Box 21, Folder 610)
  - Scott, J. Albert, 1915 (Box 21, Folder 610)
  - Scribner's (Charles) Sons(*), 1917-1920 (Box 21, Folder 611)
  - Scribner's Magazine, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 611)
  - Scripps-Howard Newspapers of Ohio, 1923 (Box 21, Folder 611)
  - Scroggs, C. J., 1924 (Box 21, Folder 611)
  - Scudder, J. W., 1894 (Box 21, Folder 611)
  - Seaman, N. S., 1894 (Box 21, Folder 612)
  - Sears, J. H.
    See: box 12, folder 328-333
  - Sears, J. M., 1902 (Box 21, Folder 612)
  - Sedgwick, Ellery
    See: box 2, folder 48
  - Sedgwick, Hubert M., 1908, 1923-1924 (Box 21, Folder 612)
  - Seiler, C. Linn, 1910-1911 (Box 21, Folder 612)
  - Selvage, Charles, 1902 (Box 21, Folder 612)
  - Senior Service Corps(*), 1917-1918, undated (Box 22, Folder 613-620)
  - Serbian Agricultural Relief Committee of America, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 621)
  - Serbian Relief Committee, 1916-1917 (Box 22, Folder 621)
  - Seton-Thompson, Grace G. (Mrs, Ernest), 1900 (Box 22, Folder 621)
  - Sewall, J. B., 1894 (Box 22, Folder 622)
  - Seward, Myron B., 1899 (Box 22, Folder 622)
  - Seymour, Charles
    See: box 30, folder 815-817
  - Seymour, George D., 1910, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 622)
  - Shanklin, W. A., 1924 (Box 22, Folder 623)
  - Shannon, Joseph W., 1894 (Box 22, Folder 623)
  - Sharpe, Albert H., 1905-1919, undated (Box 22, Folder 623)
  - Sharpe, Henry D., 1923 (Box 22, Folder 623)
  - Sharpe, Louisa D., II, 1892, 1900, undated (Box 22, Folder 623)
  - Sharpe, Lucian, undated (Box 22, Folder 623)
  - Sharpless, Issac, 1894 (Box 22, Folder 623)
  - Shaw, Ida, 1903 (Box 22, Folder 624)
  - Shaw, Joseph Alden, 1894 (Box 22, Folder 624)
  - Shaw, Ralph M., 1917 (Box 22, Folder 624)
  - Sheehan, Edgar M., 1894 (Box 22, Folder 625)
  - Sheffield, G. St. John, 1899-1900, 1909 (Box 22, Folder 625)
  - Sheffield, James R., 1907-1910 (Box 22, Folder 625)
  - Sheldon, James F., 1894 (Box 22, Folder 625)
  - Sheldon, James M., 1921 (Box 22, Folder 625)
  - Sheldon, L. P., 1905 (Box 22, Folder 625)
  - Shell, J. Kinzer, 1894 (Box 22, Folder 625)
  - Sherman, Frederick I., 1907 (Box 22, Folder 626)
  - Sherrill, Charles Hitchcock(*), 1892-1923 (Box 22, Folder 626)
  - Shevlin, Thomas L., Jr., 1905, 1909, 1911-1913 (Box 22, Folder 627)
    See also box 5, folder 144
  - Shinn, Charles H., 1900 (Box 22, Folder 628)
  - Shipman, Arthur L., 1911 (Box 22, Folder 628)
  - Shipp, Thomas R., 1915 (Box 22, Folder 628)
  - Short, Charles W., Jr., 1910 (Box 22, Folder 628)
  - Sibley, Robert, undated (Box 22, Folder 629)
  - Sievers, George W., 1911 (Box 22, Folder 629)
  - Sikes, E. W., 1892 (Box 22, Folder 629)
  - Sikes, George C., 1894 (Box 22, Folder 629)
  - Sillman, G. F., 1901 (Box 22, Folder 629)
  - Silverwood, T. P., 1912 (Box 22, Folder 629)
  - Simmons, W. D., 1894-1911 (Box 22, Folder 630)
  - Simonds, H. D., undated (Box 22, Folder 630)
  - Simons, Seward A., 1916-1922 (Box 22, Folder 631)
  - Simpkins, John, 1894-1895 (Box 22, Folder 632)
  - Simpson, George E., 1909 (Box 22, Folder 632)
  - Simpson, John R., 1908 (Box 22, Folder 632)
  - Sims, Admiral, 1919 (Box 22, Folder 632)
  - Sinclair, James C., 1919 (Box 22, Folder 632)
  - Sisson, E. G., 1912 (Box 22, Folder 632)
  - Skiddy, W. W., 1892-1905 (Box 22, Folder 633)
  - Skinner, Parker R., 1913 (Box 22, Folder 633)
  - Sloane, William M., 1894 (Box 22, Folder 633)
  - Slocum, H. W., Jr., 1891, 1893 (Box 22, Folder 633)
  - Smith Centre High School, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 634)
  - Smith, A. D., 1900 (Box 22, Folder 634)
  - Smith, A. W., 1899, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 634)
  - Smith, Andrew L., 1918-1920 (Box 22, Folder 634)
  - Smith, Arthur G., 1910 (Box 22, Folder 634)
  - Smith, Barrett, 1909 (Box 22, Folder 634)
  - Smith, C. Henry, 1906, 1924 (Box 23, Folder 635)
  - Smith, Chauncey, 1911 (Box 23, Folder 635)
  - Smith, Clarence J., 1916 (Box 23, Folder 635)
  - Smith, E. H., 1902 (Box 23, Folder 635)
  - Smith, Earl H., 1919 (Box 23, Folder 635)
  - Smith, Frank B., 1900 (Box 23, Folder 636)
  - Smith, Fred W., 1910 (Box 23, Folder 636)
  - Smith, Frederick L., 1920 (Box 23, Folder 636)
  - Smith, George Condit, 1886 (Box 23, Folder 636)
  - Smith, George Otis, 1917 (Box 23, Folder 636)
  - Smith, H. A., 1906 (Box 23, Folder 637)
  - Smith, H. Sanborn, [1883] (Box 23, Folder 637)
  - Smith, Harry A., 1923 (Box 23, Folder 637)
  - Smith, Harry L., 1905, 1910 (Box 23, Folder 637)
  - Smith, L. G., 1902 (Box 23, Folder 638)
  - Smith, Nathaniel S., 1910 (Box 23, Folder 638)
  - Smith, Paul A., 1912 (Box 23, Folder 638)
  - Smith, R. R., 1917 (Box 23, Folder 638)
  - Smith, R. S., 1912 (Box 23, Folder 638)
  - Smith, William H., 1911 (Box 23, Folder 638)
  - Smither, Henry C., 1910 (Box 23, Folder 638)
  - Smyth, Ellison A., Jr., 1892 (Box 23, Folder 638)
  - Snider, P. H., 1924 (Box 23, Folder 639)
  - Snow Neil W., 1909 (Box 23, Folder 639)
  - Solem, Oscar M., 1916 (Box 23, Folder 639)
  - South Carolina, University of, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 639)
  - South, University of the, 1892, 1899, 1902 (Box 23, Folder 639)
  - Southern California, University of, 1905 (Box 23, Folder 639)
  - Spalding (A. G.) & Bros.(*), 1891-1894, 1896-1897, 1899-1911, 1913, 1915-1918, 1920, undated (Box 23, Folder 640-647)
  - Spalding, F. S., 1894 (Box 23, Folder 648)
  - Spalding, Jesse, 1912 (Box 23, Folder 648)
  - Spaulding, W. H., 1911 (Box 23, Folder 648)
  - Spears, C. W., 1922 (Box 23, Folder 648)
  - Spee, Robert E., 1894 (Box 23, Folder 648)
  - Speir, Robert W., 1889 (Box 23, Folder 648)
  - Spencer, Selden P., 1908 (Box 23, Folder 648)
  - Sperry, W. M., 1908 (Box 23, Folder 648)
  - Spicer, William C., 1894 (Box 23, Folder 649)
  - Spitz, M. W., 1909 (Box 23, Folder 649)
  - Spooner, F. Ed., 1900 (Box 23, Folder 649)
  - Sport, Music & Drama, 1892 (Box 23, Folder 649)
  - Sporting Life, 1915, 1917 (Box 23, Folder 649)
  - Sportsman's Association, Exposition Committee
    See: box 10, folder 269
  - Sprague, Homer B., 1892 (Box 23, Folder 650)
  - Sprague, Timothy W., 1917 (Box 23, Folder 650)
  - Springfield Boys' Club, 1909 (Box 23, Folder 650)
  - Spruce, C. B., 1894 (Box 23, Folder 650)
  - Squires, Beaton H., 1907 (Box 23, Folder 650)
  - Stabb, Julius, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 650)
  - Stagg, Amos Alonzo(*), 1890, 1893-1896, 1899, 1902, 1905-1913, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 651-652)
  - Stahley, G. D., 1894 (Box 23, Folder 653)
  - Standard Encyclopedia of the Alcohol Problem, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 653)
  - Standard Oil Company, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 653)
  - Stanford, H. M., 1903 (Box 23, Folder 653)
  - Stanford University(*), 1893-1897, 1915-1921, undated (Box 23, Folder 653)
  - Stansbury, H. A., 1915-1922 (Box 23, Folder 653)
  - Starr, E. C., 1905 (Box 23, Folder 654)
  - Stauffer, Nathan P., 1904, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 654)
  - Stearns, M. M., 1910 (Box 23, Folder 655)
  - Stephens, E. Sydney, 1920-1921 (Box 23, Folder 655)
  - Stephenson, Fred M., 1900 (Box 23, Folder 655)
  - Stesel, Howard R., 1916 (Box 23, Folder 655)
  - Stevens, Albert M., 1906 (Box 23, Folder 656)
  - Stevens, Edward, 1916-1917 (Box 23, Folder 656)
  - Stevens, Elbert M., 1903 (Box 23, Folder 656)
  - Stevens, F. J., 1886, 1899-1900 (Box 23, Folder 656)
  - Stevens, G. E., 1904-1912 (Box 23, Folder 656)
  - Stevens, J. E. P., 1892 (Box 23, Folder 656)
  - Stevens, Mrs. John A., 1910 (Box 23, Folder 656)
  - Stevens, W. P., 1900 (Box 23, Folder 656)
  - Stewart, Philip B., 1886, 1893-1897, undated (Box 23, Folder 657)
  - Stillman, Walter N., 1903, 1905 (Box 23, Folder 658)
  - Stiness, Henry W., 1922 (Box 23, Folder 658)
  - Stockton (California) High School, 1894 (Box 23, Folder 658)
  - Stoddard, L. L., 1900 (Box 23, Folder 658)
  - Stoddard, Louis, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 658)
  - Stoermer, William, 1915 (Box 23, Folder 658)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps
    See: box 22, folder 626 See: box 30, folder 826-832
  - Stokes, Frederick A., 1892 (Box 23, Folder 659)
  - Stone, Frederick W., 1908 (Box 23, Folder 659)
  - Storey, Thomas A., 1907, 1917 (Box 23, Folder 659)
  - Storrow, James J.(*), 1900-1902 (Box 23, Folder 660)
  - Storrs, Lucius S., 1919 (Box 23, Folder 660)
  - Storrs, Richard S., 1905 (Box 23, Folder 660)
  - Stratford, Charles W., 1902 (Box 23, Folder 661)
  - Stratford Company, 1924 (Box 23, Folder 661)
  - Street & Finney, Inc., 1917 (Box 23, Folder 661)
  - Strength, 1924 (Box 23, Folder 661)
  - Stringer, R. S., 1913 (Box 23, Folder 661)
  - Strong Frank, 1910 (Box 23, Folder 661)
  - Strong, Tracy, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 661)
  - Stuart, T. M., Jr., 1910 (Box 23, Folder 661)
  - Sturgis, Francis S., 1910 (Box 23, Folder 661)
  - Success, 1902-1903 (Box 24, Folder 662)
  - Sullivan, James E.
    See: box 1, folder 20 See: box 1, folder 22 See: box 2, folder 38-45
  - Sullivan, Mark
  - Sully (George) & Company, 1915, 1918, 1921 (Box 24, Folder 662)
  - Summers, James C., 1899 (Box 24, Folder 662)
  - Sumner, Graham, 1910 (Box 24, Folder 662)
  - Sumner, Jennie W., 1886 (Box 24, Folder 662)
  - Sumner, William Graham, 1886 (Box 24, Folder 662)
  - Supplee, William D., 1900 (Box 24, Folder 663)
  - Susquehanna University, [ca. 1916], undated (Box 24, Folder 663)
  - Suter, Herman, 1916 (Box 24, Folder 663)
  - Sutherland, J. B., 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 663)
  - Sutphen, Van Tassel, 1906
  - Suydam, N. F., 1906 (Box 24, Folder 663)
  - Swain, H. P., 1911 (Box 24, Folder 664)
  - Swan, Joseph R., 1912, 1916-1917 (Box 24, Folder 664)
  - Swarthmore College, 1894 (Box 24, Folder 664)
  - Sweeney, Michael F., 1916-1917, undated (Box 24, Folder 665)
  - Sweet, Walter H., 1906-1921 (Box 24, Folder 665)
  - Sweetland, E. R., 1903, 1908, undated (Box 24, Folder 665)
  - Symmes, Joseph G., Jr., 1894 (Box 24, Folder 666)
  - Sypher, Howard H., 1894 (Box 24, Folder 666)
  - Syracuse University(*), 1893, 1903-1916 (Box 24, Folder 666)
  - Szle, L. Dupont, 1892-1893 (Box 24, Folder 666)
  - Taber, Harry B., 1909-1910 (Box 24, Folder 667)
  - Tackaberry, F. H., 1891 (Box 24, Folder 667)
  - Taft, A. J., 1901 (Box 24, Folder 668)
  - Taft, Henry W., 1891 (Box 24, Folder 668)
  - Taft, Horace D., 1894, [ca. 1920] (Box 24, Folder 668)
  - Taft, William Howard, 1905, 1909, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 668)
  - Talbott, N. S., 1913, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 669)
  - Tarr, E. E., 1907 (Box 24, Folder 669)
  - Taussig, Charles A., 1908 (Box 24, Folder 669)
  - Taussig, F. W., 1917 (Box 24, Folder 669)
  - Taylor, Andrew S., 1903 (Box 24, Folder 670)
  - Taylor, Edward R., 1894 (Box 24, Folder 670)
  - Taylor, H.A., 1899 (Box 24, Folder 670)
  - Taylor, Herbert W., 1916, 1918-1919 (Box 24, Folder 670)
  - Tennessee, University of, 1899, 1911 (Box 24, Folder 671)
  - Terry, C. E., 1900, 1903 (Box 24, Folder 671)
  - Terry, John T.,Jr., 1910 (Box 24, Folder 671)
  - Terry, Wyllis, 1892, 1894, 1900 (Box 24, Folder 671)
  - Tetlow, John, 1894 (Box 24, Folder 671)
  - Texas Inter-Collegiate Athletic Association, 1903 (Box 24, Folder 671)
  - Texas, University of, 1916 (Box 24, Folder 671)
  - Thacher, Sherman D., 1892 (Box 24, Folder 672)
  - Thacher, T. C., 1894-1895, 1900-1906 (Box 24, Folder 672)
  - Thacher, Thomas, 1902 (Box 24, Folder 672)
  - Thayer, George C., 1894 (Box 24, Folder 672)
  - Thayer, Harry C., 1894 (Box 24, Folder 672)
  - Their, W. W., [1920] (Box 24, Folder 672)
  - Thomas, D., 1914 (Box 24, Folder 673)
  - Thomas, F. E., 1911 (Box 24, Folder 673)
  - Thomas, I. B., 1925 (Box 24, Folder 673)
  - Thomas, J.G., 1899 (Box 24, Folder 673)
  - Thomas, T. T., 1894 (Box 24, Folder 673)
  - Thomas, W. Beach, 1903 (Box 24, Folder 673)
  - Thompson, C. F., 1917 (Box 24, Folder 674)
  - Thompson, Everard, 1900, 1907, undated (Box 24, Folder 674)
    See also: box 30, folder 822
  - Thompson, Henry B., 1894 (Box 24, Folder 674)
  - Thompson, John E. W., 1914 (Box 24, Folder 674)
  - Thompson (J. Walter) Company, 1900 (Box 24, Folder 674)
  - Thompson, M. J., 1919 (Box 24, Folder 674)
  - Thompson, Marshall, 1909, 1922 (Box 24, Folder 674)
  - Thompson, O. D., 1894-1905 (Box 24, Folder 674)
  - Thompson, S. H., Jr, undated (Box 24, Folder 674)
  - Thompson, W.G., 1906 (Box 24, Folder 674)
  - Thompson, W. W., 1905 (Box 24, Folder 674)
  - Thomson, Arthur C., 1902, 1911-1912, undated (Box 24, Folder 675)
  - Thorne, S. Brinckerhoff(*), 1896-1897, 1902, 1910, 1912, 1916-1917, 1919-1920 (Box 24, Folder 676-677)
  - Thornton, F. C., 1908 (Box 24, Folder 678)
  - Thornton, Henry W., 1894 (Box 24, Folder 678)
  - Thorp, Thomas J., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 678)
  - Thorson, I. A., 1899 (Box 24, Folder 678)
  - Thresher, Alfred A., 1890 (Box 24, Folder 679)
  - Thurston, R. H., 1894 (Box 24, Folder 679)
  - Tichenor, W. R., 1902, 1907 (Box 24, Folder 680)
  - Tilson, John Q.(*), 1917-1918, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 680)
  - Tilton, Benjamin, 1894 (Box 24, Folder 680)
  - Times (London), 1901, 1903, 1908 (Box 24, Folder 680)
  - Tisdall, Fitzgerald, 1894 (Box 24, Folder 680)
  - Tobin, L. M., 1924 (Box 24, Folder 681)
  - Todd, D. C., 1909 (Box 24, Folder 681)
  - Todd, G. Carroll, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 681)
  - Tompkins, Dean, 1897 (Box 24, Folder 681)
  - Tompkins, Ray(*), 1889, 1892, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 682-684)
  - Tooker, L. Frank, 1891 (Box 24, Folder 685)
  - Tooker, Norman B., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 685)
  - Top-Notch Magazine, 1911 (Box 24, Folder 685)
  - Torrey, H. R., 1911 (Box 24, Folder 685)
  - Town Topics, 1904, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 686)
  - Townsend, H., 1893 (Box 24, Folder 686)
  - Townsend, John B.
    See: box 20, folder 560-562
  - Townsend, Myron W., 1902 (Box 24, Folder 686)
  - Townsend, Reginald T., 1917 (Box 24, Folder 686)
  - Trafford, Percy D., 1894-1895 (Box 24, Folder 687)
  - Trail Pictures, Inc., 1922 (Box 24, Folder 687)
  - Travis, Walter J., 1902 (Box 24, Folder 687)
  - Treadwell, George L., 1910 (Box 24, Folder 688)
  - Treat, Edwin Bryant, 1910 (Box 24, Folder 688)
  - Treman, R. H., 1894 (Box 24, Folder 688)
  - Trenchard, T. G., 1894 (Box 24, Folder 688)
  - Trimble, Richard, 1910 (Box 24, Folder 689)
  - Trinity College(*), 1907 (Box 24, Folder 689)
  - Trotter, William Monroe, 1912 (Box 24, Folder 689)
  - Troup, Philip, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 689)
  - Truth, 1894 (Box 24, Folder 689)
  - Tufts College, 1894 (Box 25, Folder 690)
  - Tufts, J. A., 1894 (Box 25, Folder 690)
  - Tufts, Nathan A., 1910, 1916-1917 (Box 25, Folder 690)
  - Tulane University, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 690)
  - Tumulty, Joseph P., 1917 (Box 25, Folder 690)
  - Tunison, George M., 1914 (Box 25, Folder 690)
  - Tuttle, Emerson B., 1917 (Box 25, Folder 690)
  - Twichell, David C., [1896], 1899-1900 (Box 25, Folder 691)
  - Twichell, Joseph H., 1902, undated (Box 25, Folder 691)
  - Twitchell, Burton P., 1920 (Box 25, Folder 691)
  - Twombly, Henry B., 1894, 1909-1921 (Box 25, Folder 692)
  - Tyler, William R., 1894 (Box 25, Folder 692)
  - Tyrrell, Hy., 1899 (Box 25, Folder 692)
  - Ullman, Isaac M.(*), 1911, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 693)
  - Ullman, Louis M., 1917 (Box 25, Folder 693)
  - Umstattd, W. E., 1916 (Box 25, Folder 693)
  - Underwood, F. E., 1892 (Box 25, Folder 694)
  - Underwood, J. E., 1892 (Box 25, Folder 694)
  - Union Advertising Bureau, 1899 (Box 25, Folder 694)
  - Union College, 1894-1895 (Box 25, Folder 694)
  - United Feature Syndicate, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 694)